<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bakandamiya BMI </string>
    <string name="txtheight">Height</string>
    <string name="btncalculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="bmiResult">BMI:</string>
    <string name="txtweight">Weight</string>
    <string name="txtage">Age</string>
    <string name="txtcopyright">V 1.0 © 2022 Bakandamiya</string>
    <string name="txtcontactus">For any inquiries, suggestions or partnerships, we can be reached at:</string>

    <string name="txtAbout">Bakandamiya BMI is an app designed to provide a basic tool
        for measuring body mass index. It is meant to serve as a preliminary step to stay healthy and make informed medical decisions. It is never a substitute for medical prescription,
        so it should be used in consultation with medical personnel.\n\nThe app is created by Bakandamiya, a technology and content development company based in Nigeria. It is free for all to use.
</string>

    <string name="txtContact">Age</string>
    <string name="txtPrivacy">This Privacy Policy is here to help you understand how we treat any personal information that you share with us when you use Bakandamiya BMI Mobile Apps.
        This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect visitors’ and users’ information. Any discussion of your use of the Service in this Policy is meant to include
        your visits and other interactions with the app.\n\n<b>WHO ARE WE?</b>\nThis Mobile App (“Site”) is operated by Bakandamiya Global Concept Ltd, the global organizer of this Bakandamiya BMI mobile app, which is a Limited Liability Company registered in Nigeria. The data controller responsible for your personal data is Bakandamiya Global Concept Ltd with whom you contract as a user (“Bakandamiya”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”).\n\n<b>NO PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED</b>\nWe are happy to let every user of Bakandamiya BMI know that no personal information is collected while using the app!
</string>


    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
</resources>